

MY NAME IS





BRUNO PAES



I'm a versatile UI/UX, Product and Digital Designer with a passion for home brewing and creating engaging digital experiences.



With a strong background in web design, motion design and front-end development, I bring a unique blend of skills to every project I undertake.

> I WILL BE GLAD TO COOPERATE AND HELP TO CREATE SOMETHING SPECIAL FOR YOUR BUSINESS

> > **LET'S WORK TOGETHER**



# **SKILLS**



# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023

#### BYTE TO IT

UX/UI Designer, Product Designer and Front End Developer

2021 - 2022

#### INNOVAGENCY

UX/UI Designer, Motion Designer and Front End Developer

2018 - 2021

### BUZZBEAT

UX/UI Designer, Motion Designer and Front End Developer

2017 - 2018

# EXPRESSO

Motion Designer, UX/UI Designer and Front End Developer

2011 - 2017

# ♦ ISA, LISBON UNIVERSITY

Web-Designer, Website and Social Media Content Creator (intership)

2011 - 2016

# CULTURA NO MURO

Graphic Design, Photography, Illustration, Content Creator (voluntary work)

2007 (June - August)

#### PLANETA TANGERINA

Graphic Design, Final Art (Intership)

# **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2021

# **₱ FLAG**

Specialized Front-End Web Development Lisbon, PT

2015 - 2016

#### **ETIC**

Responsive Webdesign Lisbon, PT

2006 - 2009

# UNIVERSITY OF GLAMORGAN

BA [hons] Design for Media Cardiff, UK

2005 - 2006

# GREENWICH COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Java Programming (level 2) London, UK

2005 - 2006

# ESCOLA FERNANDO LOPES GRAÇA

Computer Science (12° ano) Parede, PT

# **VOLUNTARY WORK**

I am one of the founders of the "Cultura no Muro" Association, located in Parede, which promotes cultural initiatives and fosters critical thinking. In 2011, the Association won the participatory budget of Cascais with the objective of restoring the SMUP building (now 124 years old), where it conducts its activities.

